Stewart L. Udall papers, 1950-2010
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series I: Campaign and Congressional Materials, 1954-1960
  - 85th Congress, 1957-1958
    - Political Campaign: Frank Barry Issue. 1958 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Political Campaign: Miscellaneous Material. 1958 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Political Campaign: "1958 Campaign Ammo." 1958 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Political Campaign: Scrapbook of Clippings. 1958 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - 86th Congress, 1958-1960
    - 86th Congress: Administration, House of Representatives-Committees, Miscellaneous Material, Voting Record. 1959-1960 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, House of Representatives-Telephone, Rent, Office Supplies, etc. 1959-1960 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Stationary Room-Sales Slips, Statements. 1959-1960 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Stewart Udall's Congressional Reports-Includes Statements and News Releases. 1959-1960 (Box 44, Folder 4-5)
    - 86th Congress: Administration: Miscellaneous: Stewart Udall's " Frosh Congressmen Orientation" Seminars. 1959-1960 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - 86th Congress: Administration. 1959-1960 (Box 44)
      Box Also Includes:
      House Rules and Manual, 86th Congress
      Cannon's Procedure in the House of Representatives, 1959
      Gavel: autographed by Speaker of the House Sam Rayburn, presented to Stewart Udall "on the occasion of his first opportunity to preside over the Committee of the whole House," February 18, 1959
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Clippings-Minority Group Rights (Includes Stewart Udall's Brotherhood Week Speech, Phoenix). 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Speeches. 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Clippings-Stewart Udall (Miscellaneous and Personal). 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Clippings-"The Case for Public Spending", Budget. 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Clippings-"The Presidency." 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Clippings-Russia, Goldwater. 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Stewart Udall in the Congressional Record, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Correspondence to Congressional Record Clerk. 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Library of Congress. 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Patronage. 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Contributions. 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Stewart Udall's Questionnaire. 1959 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Stewart Udall's Questionnaire with Replies Alphabetically Arranged. 1960 (Box 47, Folder 2-4)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Stewart Udall's Questionnaire-Coconino County Response. 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 5-8)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Stewart Udall's Questionnaire-Gila County Response. 1959-1960 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Stewart Udall's Questionnaire-Pima County Response. 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Stewart Udall's Questionnaire-Santa Cruz County Response. 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Stewart Udall's Questionnaire-Yavapai County Response. 1959-1960 (Box 48, Folder 3-9)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Stewart Udall's Questionnaire-Cochise County Response. 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 1-6)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Stewart Udall's Questionnaire-Maricopa County Response. 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Stewart Udall's Questionnaire-Mohave County Response. 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 8-9)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Stewart Udall's Questionnaire-Navajo County Response. 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Stewart Udall's Questionnaire-Apache, Greenlee, Graham, Pinal, and Yuma County Responses (Also Includes Unidentified, and Out-of-State). 1959-1960 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Inter-Office Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Office Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Correspondence-Radio and Television. 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Correspondence-Arizona State Legislature. 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Correspondence-Arizona Agencies and Arizona Problems. 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 5-6)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 7-8)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Personal Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Correspondence (Cranks). 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Correspondence-Stewart Udall's Private Law Practice. 1959-1960 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Correspondence-Appropriations. 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Correspondence-Budget, Economy, Public Debt. 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 3-4)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Correspondence-Committee on Government Operations. 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Correspondence-Committee on Un-American Activities. 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Correspondence-Foreign Affaris, Foreign Aid. 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 7-8)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Correspondence-Indian Affairs (Hawley Lake Road on Ft. Apache Indian Reservation. 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Correspondence-Indian Affairs, Miscellaneous (Includes Correspondence on the NBC Production of the "Ira Hayes Story." 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Correspondence-Politics. 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Correspondence-Politics (Frank H. Jones). 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Correspondence-Supreme. 1959-1960 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Requests-For Information. 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Requests-For Assistance. 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Requests-For Opinions, Photographs. 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Requests-For Meetings, Tours, Tickets. 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Requests-For USDA Yearbooks. 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 5-6)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Requests-For Various Publications. 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Requests-For U.S. Flags. 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Requests-For Jobs. 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 9-10)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Requests-Letters of Introduction and Recommendation. 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Invitations-To Attend Dedication Ceremonies. 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Invitations-To Speak and Participate in Discussions. 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Invitations-To Attend Meetings, Banquets, Social Events. 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 3-6)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Publications and Pictures Received. 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 7-8)
    - 86th Congress: Administration-Congratulations (Outgoing). 1959-1960 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Interior- Miscellaneous and General Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Interior-Bureau of Indian Affairs, Oraibi High School Closing. 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Interior-Bureau of Indian Affairs, Various Topics. 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Interior-Bureau of Indian Affairs, Miscellaneous Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Interior-Bureau of Land Management, General Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 5-6)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Interior-Bureau of Land Management (Includes Tucson Mountain Park Correspondence). 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Interior-Bureau of Land Management (Includes Tucson Mountain Park Clippings). 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Interior-Bureau of Reclamation, Colorado River Storage Project. 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 1-3)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Interior-Bureau of Reclamation-Yuma Water Contract. 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Interior-Bureau of Reclamaion-New Frontier, Arizona. 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Interior-Bureau of Reclamation, Miscellaneous Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 6-7)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Interior-Fish and Wildlife Service. 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Interior-Office of the Solicitor. 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Interior-National Park Service. 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Interior-Office of Saline Water. 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 2-3)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Interior-Office of Territories, Frank Freeland Case. 1959-1960 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Health, Education, and Welfare-Office of Education. 1959-1960 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Health, Education, and Welfare-Public Health Service, Radio-active Pollution of the Colorado River. 1959-1960 (Box 57, Folder 2-3)
    - 86th Congress. Administration, Department of the Health, Education, and Welfare-Public Health Service (Indian TB Patients at Veterans Hospitals and Oshrin Hospital. 1959-1960 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Health, Education, and Welfare-Public Health Service (Housing for Staff, Indian Hospital Gallup, New Mexico. 1959-1960 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Health, Education, and Welfare-Public Health Service, Miscellaneous. 1959-1960 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Health, Education, and Welfare-Social Security Administration. 1959-1960 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Health, Education, and Welfare-Miscellaneous and Various. 1959-1960 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of Agriculture-Commodity Stablilization Service. 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of Agriculture-Forest Service. 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of Agriculture-Soil Conservation Service. 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of Agriculture-Miscellaneous Agencies. 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of Commerce-Bureau of the Census. 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of Commerce-Bureau of Public Roads. 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of Commerce-Various Agencies. 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of Justice-Immigration and Naturalization Service. 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of Justice-Miscelleneous and Various. 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of Labor. 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Treasury Department-Bureau of Customs and Miscellaneous. 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Treasury Department-Internal Revenue Service. 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of Defense-General Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of Defense-Transportation of Military Personnel Household Goods. 1959-1960 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Army-General Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 59, Folder 3-5)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Army-Ft. Huachuca Matters. 1959-1960 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Army-Yuma Testing Station. 1959-1960 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Army-Corps of Engineers. 1959-1960 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Navy-General Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 59, Folder 9-10)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Navy-Yuma Mesa Irrigation and Drainage District (Navy Condemnation). 1959-1960 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Service Academies-Appointments. 1959-1960 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Air Force-Davis-Monthan AFB, Tucson, Arizona. 1959-1960 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Air Force-Titan Missile Base, Tucson, Arizona. 1959-1960 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Air Force-Williams AFB, Chandler, Arizona. 1959-1960 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Air Force-Lt. LW Roberson, Jr. Case. 1959-1960 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of the Air Force-General Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 60, Folder 5-6)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of State-Visas. 1959-1960 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of State-Passports, International Exchange Program. 1959-1960 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Department of State-"Korean File." 1959-1960 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Civil Aeronautics Board-Dockett #9999, Frontier Airlines. 1959-1960 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Civil Aeronautics Board-Dockett #10038, Bonanza Airlines. 1959-1960 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Civil Aeronautics Board-Various. 1959-1960 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      Docket #5395-Southern Rocky Mountain Area
      Docket #7672-Frontier Airlines
      Docket #7984-Southern Transcontinental Service
      Docket #9185-Kanab-Page-Glen Canyon Area
      Docket #10738-Southwestern Area Local Service
    - 86th Congress: Administration, General Services Administration- Includes Correspondence Regarding Federal Buildings in Holbrook, Nogales, and Phoenix. 1959-1960 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Small Business Administration. 1959-1960 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Veterans Administration-Miscellaneous. 1959-1960 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Veterans Administration (Arranged Alphabetically). 1959-1960 (Box 61, Folder 7-9)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Office of Civil and Defense Mobilization. 1959-1960 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Federal Communications Commission-General Correspondence (Includes Correspondence Regarding Transmitter Tower for Channels 4 & 13, Tucson, Arizona. 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Federal Communications Commission-TV Booster Stations Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 2-4)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Federal Communications Commission-TV Booster Stations Petitions. 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Federal Housing Administration-Housing at Sierra Vista and Ft. Huachuca, Arizona. 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Federal Housing Administration-Miscellaneous Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, International Boundary and Water Commission. 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Interstate Commerce Commission-Routing of Southern Pacific Trains. 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Post Office Department. 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Atomic Energy Commission. 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Civil Service Commission. 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Tariff Commission-Long-staple Cotton. 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 5-6)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Tariff Commission-Meat. 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Tariff Commission-Shrimp. 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Tariff Commission-Miscellaneous Publications. 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Housing and Home Finance Agency. 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - 86th Congress: Administration, Railroad Retirement Board. 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation,Udall Bills List. 1959-1960 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Stewart Udall's Bills. January 1959-May 1960 (Box 64, Folder 2-24)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Udall Bills. June 1959-January 1960 (Box 65, Folder 1-26)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Agriculture-Farm Labor. 1959-1960 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Agriculture-Farm Price Supports & Surplus Commodities. 1959-1960 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Agriculture-Sugar Beets and Cuban Sugar. 1959-1960 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Agriculture-Miscellaneous and Various. 1959-1960 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Taxes-Dividend Payments. 1959-1960 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Taxes-Gasoline and Highway Construction. 1959-1960 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Taxes-Income and Internal Revenue Code. 1959-1960 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Taxes-H.R. 12381, Escise Tax on Telephone Service. 1959-1960 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Taxes-Miscellaneous and Various. 1959-1960 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Education-National Defense Education Act. 1959-1960 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Education-Federal Aid Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 67, Folder 2-3)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Education-Federal Aid Bills, Hearings, Miscellaneous Material. 1959-1960 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Education-Federal Aid Clippings. 1959-1960 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Education-Federal Aid, Background Material, Notes. 1959-1960 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Education-Federal Aid, Requests for Publications. 1959-1960 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Education-Federal Aid, Goldwater Debate, "Fact Brief." 1959-1960 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Education-Federal Aid, Goldwater Debate Backround Material. 1959-1960 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Education-Federal Aid, Goldwater Debate Stewart Udall Notes and Clippings. 1959-1960 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Education-Federal Aid, Goldwater Debate Correspondence and Fan Mail. 1959-1960 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Health and Welfare-H.R. 4700, Forand Bill to Amend the Social Security Act and Internal Revenue Code. 1959-1960 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Health and Welfare-H.R. 4700, Against. 1959-1960 (Box 68, Folder 2-3)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Health and Welfare-H.R. 4700, For. 1959-1960 (Box 68, Folder 4-5)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Health and Welfare-Federal Employees Health Insurance. 1959-1960 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Health and Welfare-Social Security Bills. 1959-1960 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Health and Welfare-Various Bills on Chemical Additives. 1959-1960 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Health and Welfare-Miscellaneous Bills and Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, S. 659, H.R. 4639-Home Rule for Washington, DC. 1959-1960 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Labor -H.R. 9070, S. 2643-Situs Pickering. 1959-1960 (Box 69, Folder 1-2)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Labor-H.R. 4488, S. 1046-Minimum Wage. 1959-1960 (Box 69, Folder 3-4)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Labor-Miscellaneous Bills and Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Labor Reform-Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 70, Folder 1-5)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Labor Reform-Udall's Notes, Analyses of Various Bills, Miscellaneous Material. 1959-1960 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Labor Reform-H.R. 8342, Elliott Bill. 1959-1960 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Labor Reform-H.R. 8490, Shelley Bill. 1959-1960 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Labor Reform -H.R. 8400, Landrum-Griffin Bill. 1959-1960 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Labor Reform-H.R. 8400, For (Mimeo Form Letter). 1959-1960 (Box 71, Folder 4-5)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Labor Reform-H.R. 8400, For (Pen Pal Reply). 1959-1960 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Labor Reform-H.R. 8400, For (Out-of-State). 1959-1960 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Labor Reform-H.R. 8400, For (Acknowledged by Personal Letter). 1959-1960 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Labor Reform-S. 1555. 1959-1960 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Labor Reform-Archibald Cox. June-September 1959 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Labor Reform-Clippings. 1959-1960 (Box 71, Folder 11-12)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Reclamation and Conservation-Lower Colorado River and "Squatter Problem." 1959-1960 (Box 72, Folder 1-3)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Reclamation and Conservation-S. 3180, Rainbow Bridge. 1959-1960 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Reclamation and Conservation-Various Wilderness Bills. 1959-1960 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Reclamation and Conservation-Miscellaneous Bills and Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Reclamation and Conservation-Background Material for Game Protective Association Speech on Wilderness Bills. 1959-1960 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Mining-H.R. 1930, Domestic Manganese Program. 1959-1960 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Mining-Bills to Amend the Helium Act. 1959-1960 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Mining-Miscellaneous Bills and Correspondence. 1959-1960 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Armed Services. 1959-1960 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Veterans- H.R. 11045, National Service Life Insurance. 1959-1960 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Veterans-H.R. 9336, World War I Pension. 1959-1960 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - 86th Congress: Legislation, Veterans-H.R. 1181, World War I Pension. 1959-1960 (Box 73, Folder 4-5)